And she doesn't want any rugs.
她还不想铺地毯.
Yvonne, Klara may be our strangest client ever.
Yvonne, Klara也许是我们碰到的最古怪的客户了.
She's not so bad.
她没这么糟糕.
You must be joking.
你一定是在开玩笑.
Hey. She knows what she wants and she can pay for it.
Hey. 她很清楚自己想要什么, 而且她也付得起钱.
What's the problem?
你说她有什么问题呢?
She doesn't know what she wants.
她不知道自己想要什么.
She can't have known.
她不可能知道.
She's been through a dozen designers.
她都已经换了十几个设计师了.
Nan, she's not that hard to read.
Nan, 其实要了解她的设计意图并不是那么困难.
We may not like what we read.
也许我们不喜欢她的设计意图.
But she is the boss.
可她是老板呀.
That's another thing. We're freelance.
那得另当别论了. 我们是自由职业者.
We're supposed to be our own bosses.
我们得自己当自己的老板.
Freelance just means everyone is your boss.
当自山职业者就意味着人人都是你的老板.
But I'm still glad I left my old job.
不过我还是很高兴离开了原来的工作.
I'd rather have a crazy rich lady tell me what to do,
我宁愿让一个古怪的富婆支使我去做这做那,
than an office full of state attorneys, thank you.
也不愿意坐在满满一办公室的州检察官中间, 多谢了.
Richard was not a bad boss.
Richard可是个不错的老板.
No. But some of the others could have been prison guards.
说得对. 可有些人就像监狱看守一样盯着你.
Anyway, who would you rather look at:
再说, 你宁愿看哪个：
a State House lawyer, or Antonio?
是州议会的律师, 还是Antonio呢?
Please. Antonio is very strange.
得了吧.  Antonio这个人非常古怪.
Nan. It's an interesting project.
Nan, 这次的项目还是挺有趣的.
She's paying us for our time.
我们所花的时间她都是付费的.
We'll do a good job.
我们会干得很出色的.
I guarantee she will change her mind about what she wants.
我敢打保票她中途又会改变主意的.
She might.
也许吧.
She will.
肯定会.